Really quickly, I just want to talk to folks who consider themselves artists.
One of your key tenets as an artist is to protect other artists' work.
When you are involved in the creation of their work, you protect other artists' work.
What does protection mean? Protection means showing up.
Protection means when you can't show up, making sure that your role is covered.
Protection means not divulging any details that aren't supposed to be divulged.
Protection means giving your heart, not just your mind, to whatever role you have in that art.
When we talk about art, we're talking about things that are being created from the heart and mind, right?
And I don't think enough of us understand that and we need to self-check that.
Because sometimes we think we just have a job. No, you have a journey.
And when you are working with other people's art as a part of your journey, understand that each piece is stepping you forward.
Sometimes you find yourself in a position where you don't even like the person.
It doesn't matter. Art is bigger than you.
And even if you don't like that person, but you know that they are making art,
you have a responsibility to show up authentically and genuinely.
Yeah. So shout out to all my artisans out there.